[
   {
      "question":"Which episode number is the first Star Wars film?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"IV",
      "choices":[
         "I",
         "V",
		 "IV",
		 "VI"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What was Han Solo frozen in?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Carbonite",
      "choices":[
         "Ice",
         "Water Ice",
         "Nitrogen liquid",
         "Carbonite"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"And for how long was he frozen?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"About one year",
      "choices":[
         "About one year",
         "Four year",
         "Three",
         "One Year"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"How many forms of communication is C-3P0 fluent in?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Over 6 million",
      "choices":[
		 "Over 2 million",
		 "3 million",
         "Over 6 million",
         "Over 10 Billion"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Where does Rey find Luke Skywalker?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Ahch-To",
      "choices":[
         "Batuu",
         "Bogano",
         "Ahch-To",
         "Jakku"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who killed Mace Windu?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Darth Sidious",
      "choices":[
         "Darth Vader",
         "Darth Plagueis",
         "Darth Sidious",
         "Darth Maul"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What is the name of Anakin's stepbrother?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Owen Lars",
      "choices":[
         "Shmi Skywalker",
         "Owen Lars",
         "Luke Skywalker",
         "Leia Organa"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who was Boba Fett's father?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Jango Fett",
      "choices":[
         "Din Djarin",
         "Cade Bane",
         "Hondo Ohnaka",
         "Jango Fett"
      ]
   },
   {
      "What was Galen Erso's nickname for his daughter?",
      "category":"Satr Wars",
      "answer":"Stardust",
      "choices":[
         "Stardust",
         "Little Star",
         "Jyn",
         "Shine Star"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What is the name of the female member of the Jedi High Council who is of the same species as Yoda?",
      "category":"Satr Wars",
      "answer":"Yaddle",
      "choices":[
         "Oola",
         "Shaak-Ti",
         "Asajj Ventress",
         "Yaddle"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What model of aircraft did Luke use to bullseye Womp Rats ?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"T-16 skyhopper",
      "choices":[
         "P-47",
         "T-16 skyhopper",
         "X-Wing",
         "T-26 skyhopper"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Han Solo boasted that the Millennium Falcon made the Kessel Run in less than how many parsecs?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"12 parsecs",
      "choices":[
         "12 parsecs",
         "20 parsecs",
         "30 parsecs",
         "50 parsecs"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who was the first character to speak in the first Star Wars film, A New Hope?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"C-3PO",
      "choices":[
         "Darth Vader",
         "Moff Tarkin",
         "Leia Organa",
         "C-3PO"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Princess Leia tells Grand Moff Tarkin the rebel base is located on what planet?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Dantooine",
      "choices":[
         "Tatooine",
         "Alderaan",
         "Dantooine",
         "Hoth"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who was Luke Skywalker's gunner during the Battle of Hoth?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Dak Ralter",
      "choices":[
         "Carson Teva",
         "Dak Ralter",
         "Trapper Wolf",
         "Jib Dodger"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What species is Greedo?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Rodian",
      "choices":[
         "Gungans",
         "Rodian",
         "Zeltrons",
         "Ewoks"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"In which movie did Yoda NOT appear?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"A New Hope",
      "choices":[
         "The Empire Strikes Back",
         "Return of the Jedi",
         "A New Hope",
         "The Phantom Menace"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"In what system are Han and Leia before traveling to Bespin?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Anoat",
      "choices":[
         "Bakura",
         "Corellian",
         "Dagobah",
         "Anoat"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What species is native to Endor?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Ewok",
      "choices":[
         "Wookies",
         "Ewok",
         "Gungans",
         "Rodians"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Which actor is the only one who's appeared in every single Star Wars movie to date?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Anthony Daniels",
      "choices":[
         "Mark Hamill",
         "Harrison Ford",
         "Anthony Daniels",
         "Ewan McGregor"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Which stormtrooper wasn't able to complete his mission in Star Wars: The Force Awakens?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"FN-2187",
      "choices":[
         "FN-8721",
         "FN-1278",
         "FN-2187",
         "FN-7812"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What were Padmé's last words?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Obi-Wan...there...is good in him. I know there is.",
      "choices":[
         "Obi-Wan...there...is good in him. I know there is.",
         "Obi-Wan...please take care of them"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What kind of vehicle did Rey live in?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"AT-AT",
      "choices":[
         "TIE fighter",
         "Imperial star destroyer",
         "AT-AT",
         "AT-ST"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"According to Master Yoda, how many Sith are always out there?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Two",
      "choices":[
         "Two",
         "Three",
         "Four",
         "One"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What happened to Anakin Skywalker during the first battle with Count Dooku?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"He lost his right arm",
      "choices":[
         "He kill Count Dooku",
         "He lost a leg",
         "He lost his right arm"         
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who played the part of Commander Cody?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Temuera Morrison",
      "choices":[
         "Cliff Curtis",
         "Ian McDiarmid",
         "Temuera Morrison",
         "Diego Luna"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who killed Jabba?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Princess Leia",
      "choices":[
         "Lando Calrissian",
         "Luke Skywalker",
         "Princess Leia",
         "Han Solo"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What did Luke Skywalker lose in his fight with Darth Vader?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"His right hand",
      "choices":[
         "A arm",
         "His ligth saber",
         "His right hand",
         "His Father"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What did Jar Jar Binks end up owing Qui-Gon Jinn after being rescued during the invasion of Naboo?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"An honor debt",
      "choices":[
         "His life",
         "A ship",
         "10 in credits",
         "An honor debt"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What did Owen Lars tell Luke about his father?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"He was a navigator on a spice freighter.",
      "choices":[
         "A pilot on the republic army",
         "He was killed by Darth Vader",         
         "He was a navigator on a spice freighter."
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What is the color of C-3PO's arm in Star Wars: The Force Awakens?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Red",
      "choices":[
         "Silver",
         "Gold",
         "Red",
         "White"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"This city is the only one located on two continents.",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Geonosis",
      "choices":[
         "Batuu",
         "Geonosis",
         "Jakku",
         "Naboo"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who adopted Padmé Amidala's daughter?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Bail Organa",
      "choices":[
         "Bail Organa",
         "Beru Lars",
         "Hera Syndula",
         "Breha Organa"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What was the job that Finn told Han Solo he had at Starkiller Base?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Sanitation",
      "choices":[
         "Guard",
         "Solider",
         "Sanitation",
         "Security"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Where were the Hoth sequences filmed?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Norway",
      "choices":[
         "IceLand",
         "Alaska",
         "Switzerland",
         "Norway"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What name does Obi-Wan Kenobi go by on Tatooine?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Ben",
      "choices":[
         "Kenobi",
         "Obi-Wan",
         "Ben Kenobi",
         "Ben"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"How old was Anakin during the battle on Geonosis?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"20",
      "choices":[
         "30",
         "33",
         "25",
         "20"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who freed Princess Leia from her chains at Jabba's palace?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"R2-D2",
      "choices":[
         "C-3PO",
         "Luke Skywalker",
         "R2-D2",
         "Han Solo"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"How did Luke manage to get into Jabba's palace?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"He used an ancient Jedi mind trick on Bib Fortuna.",
      "choices":[
         "He used an ancient Jedi mind trick on Bib Fortuna.",
         "He kills everyone until he gets into the palace",
		 "He used a disguise",
		 "He used the force"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who first and most famously played the part of Chewbacca?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Peter Mayhew",
      "choices":[
         "Joonas Suotamo",
         "Peter Mayhew",
         "Nick Pritchard"         
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who fixed the hyperdrive on the Millennium Falcon?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"R2-D2",
      "choices":[
         "R2-D2",
         "Han Solo",
         "Pricess Leia",
         "Chewbacca"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who killed Jango Fett was Mace Windu.",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"True",
      "choices":[
         "True",
         "False"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"What species was Yoda?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Unknown",
      "choices":[
         "Twi'lek",
         "Rodian",
         "Neimoidian",
         "Unknown"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who are the comedians behind the voice for BB-8?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Ben Schwartz and Bill Hader",
      "choices":[
         "Ben Schwartz",         
         "Bill Hader",
         "Ben Schwartz and Bill Hader"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"When Obi-Wan performed the blood test on Anakin, how high was the Midi-chlorian count?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"More than 20,000",
      "choices":[
         "20,000",
         "30,000",
         "More than 50,000",
         "More than 20,000"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"According to the Emperor, what was Luke's weakness?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"His faith in his friends",
      "choices":[
         "His ability with the ligth saber",
         "The love for his father",
         "His anger",
         "His faith in his friends"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Which bounty hunter was trying to capture Han when Greedo arrived first?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Danz Borin",
      "choices":[
         "Boba Fett",
         "Bossk",
         "Danz Borin",
         "Jango Fett"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"Who taught Lando Calrissian how to pilot a ship?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Han Solo",
      "choices":[
         "Han Solo",
         "His Father",
         "Luke Skywalker",
         "Hera Syndulla"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question":"How many lightsabers does General Grievous wield in his fight with Obi-Wan on Utapau?",
      "category":"Star Wars",
      "answer":"Four",
      "choices":[
         "Five",
         "Two",
         "Six",
         "Four"
      ]
   }
]